Every time the rain no longer falls, and I
see the sky, I think the rain is falling.
Back to when I was a child,
who could only cry,
blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought,
one day I will be stronger.
Bridery and gratitude
fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was
before, or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure, but until
I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead!
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now.
Though times are on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest of all can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back?
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now.
Though time's not on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way everything will
take what I hold dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see?
We're good!
Ace is still alive, guys!
Hey, pull it together, pal.
That power, it came
from Ace's brother, huh?
What the?
I almost passed out back there.
That was the conqueror spirit
like Pops and Shanks use.
Damn that kid is full of surprises, huh?
I don't think he realizes
what he just did.
I tell you boys we got some
scary stuff right here!
He didn't learn that
power he was born with it.
Just like Pops.
If your will is weak, stand back!
He's not just another rookie.
Conqueror's spirit, huh?
We can't forget he's the son of dragon.
That's what we get for
underestimating him!
What next, Vice Admiral?
My energy hormones didn't do that What
hat did you pull those powers out of?
Power?
What do you mean?
We'll discuss it later.
He's not aware of it.
That means we can't count
on him using it again.
Either way, it's no wonder the
people are so drawn to him?
The apple doesn't fall far
from the tree, does it, dragon?
Do not let that boy
escape this battlefield.
If he does, he'll turn
into a dire threat to us.
Dead or alive, you take him down.
Focus on Whitebeard first.
He may be a monster, but he's injured.
Take him down, then go for the kid.
After Straw Hat, hurry!
Stop and listen to me!
What's wrong?
There's a new plan.
I'm either gonna live or I'm gonna die.
So back up Straw Hat with
everything you've got!
Ace's brother, why?
They're coming straight at ya! Watch out!
I know you.
You're Dome, the Bohemian Knight, correct?
Vice Admiral Momonga,
pleasure to meet you.
To the Calvert brothers,
it sucks to be you.
You gotta fight us!
Thunderlord Mock!
Pardon me, Vice Admiral, but I require
a moment of your time if you would.
We've got some friends!
If Whitebeard says to lend you a
hand, then we're on it in a flash!
Chase is right there, Straw Hat.
No way they're gonna stop all of us!
Whitebeard's allies are
backing up Straw Hat.
This does not look good.
Who are you guys?
Never mind that.
Keep running.
The Navy forces are
focused on Pops right now.
So this might be your only chance to
slip past the admirals and move in.
We're slamming them all at
once, so wait for your opening.
Hey, not bad.
I think they like you.
The greatest pirate in the
world gave his seal of approval.
Ace may be your brother,
but he's Whitebeard's son,
you know, and he trusts you with his life.
So why don't you stop trying to
be coy and rise to the occasion,
you cocky little snot?
I don't care what that old man wants,
and I don't care what he thinks either.
I only came here to do one thing.
I don't need anyone's approval for that.
The pirates are gaining headway on us.
They're about to break through.
We need backup in a hurry.
With all due respect, maybe
we should change plans.
Not yet.
If we have a chance to defeat
Whitebeard, then we must take it.
Everyone move in now.
If he falls, then it's only a
matter of time for the rest of them.
One or 100 doesn't matter.
You can stand in line or
you can all die at once.
He's still up.
What's it going to take?
We think alike, brat.
As long as Ace goes home,
nothing else matters.
Show me the will of D.
Show me the future.
Even if my days are
numbered, I can see tomorrow.
Blazing through this battlefield.
Oh, Hawkeye.
This could get nasty.
Did you hear me?
Thanks.
It's the president's order.
For now, we're still allies. Go.
Mr. One, I believe.
Look out!
Crocodile Two?
Stop sleeping on the job, Mr. One.
I thought it was like old times,
but maybe prison made me soft.
You are needed here, Straw Hat.
Get moving before I change my mind.
This won't end well.
Are you certain?
I'm not in the mood to put up
with your crap or anyone else's.
If you want to fight,
then shut up and do it.
Luffy I'm here I'll do everything
in my power to aid you.
Target is Monkey D Luffy open fire.
Boa Hancock incite aborting the attack.
That's enough.
Are you out of your damn mind?
This isn't the first time you've gotten
in the way, but it will be the last.
What are you trying to
accomplish here anyway?
You're going to lose your warlord status.
You foolish, misshapen man-child.
Your ignorance is an affront to my beauty.
My what now?
I shall set a pearl of wisdom before you.
Love is always a
hurricane, you little pig.
Big, you're insane, aren't you?
Hishman Karate!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Jinbei, I can handle this, damn it.
I said to leave me and help Straw
Hat get to the scaffold, didn't I?
Sorry, friend, but I'm
not one of your pirates.
That means I don't have to
listen to a word you say.
Have it your way, then.
Everyone else has already done their part.
Now you do yours.
Keep on running and don't look back.
For better or worse, it's our turn now.
Look, I'm sorry to make you do this
when I know you're still recovering,
but we need your skills in particular
No apologies necessary.
I assure you I shall give it my best
They made a bridge!
It's Sinasuma of the Revolutionary Army!
Is that handy or what? Thanks!
Straw Hutt's headed
straight for the scaffold!
Stop him!
Sorry, too busy to do it myself!
What are you doing?
Block his path! We can't, sir! See?
These pirates are blocking us!
We can't get past! Fools!
Use your guns!
Cannoneers, open fire!
Damn! It's them!
The Whitebeard Pirates team of commanders.
Pop said to watch your back.
So keep running, we got this!
Everyone push, we're breaking through!
Here he comes, man!
Come, come!
Battleaxe!
Take it straight to the
top. You got it! Thanks!
He's getting away!
Death wing!
If you really want to
rumble, then step right up!
Hee-haw!
Now you just keep on
shining, Strawboy. It worked!
He's gonna make it!
We got this!
We really got this!
It's not over!
Pull him down!
Strawhat! Savings!
Yeah, it's all you! Here on out!
I've got to admit, I didn't think
Whitebeard would gamble it all on you.
It's been a fun ride.
But don't kid yourself, boy.
Well, don't that beat all.
It's gonna be a good show.
Why don't you just sit back and watch?
Reef?
We did it!
I'm here!
Is Garp gonna fight too?
Grandpa!
Get out of the way
I'm not moving a damned edge
I'm a vice-admiral of the Navy
I've been fighting
pirates since long before
you were born and I ain't stopping today
You're not my grandson
here you are the pirate
Straw Hat Luffy and I'll
fight you to the death
This is the path that you chose to take!
You and your brother alike.
The bridge is going to
give out, straw boy!
You got to move it or lose
it, whatever it takes!
Don't give up!
Almost there.
You want to pass me?
Then treat me like any other marine
you've faced and fight for your life!
Grandpa, this kind of hurts.
Why do you want me to fight
these dumb monkeys all day?
It's your training.
Training sucks.
For one, I have to get hit all
the time and for two, I'm hungry.
Don't be a baby.
You're gonna be a fine marine someday.
Just like me.
Oh, I'm gonna be a pirate.
Marines are all lame.
Huh?
You little punk
The monkeys hit hard, but
you're even worse, Gramps
I'm not hurting you!
Just move!
If you don't strike me dead,
then you'll lose Ace Shut up!
You can't just cry till you get
your way I won't show you mercy!
You're a pirate, Luffy!
That makes you my enemy!
Luffy!
Garp!
Damn it, this is all wrong.
How the hell am I supposed to feel?
Pops, Luffy, my friends.
They're going to save me,
but they're pushing through a
sea of their own blood to do it.
I'm sick.
These are tears of joy.
Even after all I've done, I want to live.
He took down Garp?
They're family after all damn it.
Look at that I believe
he just might make it.
Change your mind I thought
you said he couldn't do it.
I didn't say he could save
Ace now that he's at the top.
They'll die together that's all.
Shut your mouth.
You let your guard down.
Finally, I'm here.
Hold on.
Take this.
It's the key to your brother's handcuffs.
I got the key right here.
That's great, but how?
What the hell is that?
That's Sengoku's power.
I've never seen it.
Damn, he's huge.
Figure all your life, but you're
trapped in the palm of my hand.
This is insane!
A gold statue?
That's not something you
should have, Straw Hat.
Let's fix that, shall we?
No! The key! Take aim!
Wait until I give the
order, but prepare to fire!
Oh, crap!
I lost it!
You've dug your own grave.
You're a criminal as well, Straw Hat.
I've had enough!
I will execute the both of you.
Right here, it was my own fair hands.
My goodness.
I think I must have passed
out for a moment there.
Strawhead, what?
Wait, three?
Why are you here?
What is that thing?
Three, quick, protect Ace with the wall!
I'm not losing now!
I've got a giant balloon!
Candy War!
What's she doing?
The whole scaffold's coming down what
happened up there ain't you still alive?
This is awful I'll make a key
get those cuffs off him and hurry!
You got it look captain buggy
that's where brother three
wins holy crap I thought he
Hightailed it out of the stump,
but now he's right in the middle of it.
Also, what the hell is he wearing?
Where's the replacement?
What could possibly be taking him so long?
Well, it was short notice that
we don't do this very often.
Hey, you ready?
Fine, let's move.
Frankly I couldn't care
less about your brother.
I'm here.
Out of respect for my late comrade.
Laugh at me if you like.
But here's your key.
Why would I laugh at that?
Fire.
Blow the tippets before
they hit the ground.
Here.
Good luck.
Thanks three.
That doesn't look good. Luffy!
Hey, stop!
Brother 3!
That is an ugly way to go.
Those handcuffs are sea prism stone.
Firefist's power won't
be able to save him.
Pretty sure we got
Straw Hat in there, too.
What is that?
It looks like a tunnel of flames!
Ever since you were little, you've never
listened to a word I said, have you?
Then you run off and do something crazy.
Like old times, huh, Luffy?
They're alive!
Well, of course!
It's a true miracle!
Hey, I see them!
Look there in the flames!
Let's go!